Call me when you're in a pinch!
Chant this three times in your mind!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
Enter
the
hero!
If you do that,
I'll
come to you
The zipper was up top, but the fly was wide open!
（部員）
ジッパーは上に付いてんのに
チャックは全開でさ
Someone pointed it out, but I ignored them.
（部員）
せっかく注意してくれたのに
シカトしちゃって
２限の終わりから４時間近くだぜ
I was like that for almost four
hours after second period ended.
And nobody told me!
その間
誰も俺を注意してくれねえの
Ain't that funny, Smile?
（部員）
スマイル おかしくねえ？
（スマイル）うん おかしい
Yeah, it's funny.
You seriously never smile.
（部員）
お前 ホントに笑わねえよね
Where's Peco today?
（部員）今日 ペコは？
Dunno.
知らない
（部員）
あいつ いねえと—
If he's not here, Oota will start griping again.
また大田(おおた)さん
うるさいぜ
お前ら 目の上の
たんこぶだし
Yeah, you two are a thorn in his side. Do you get that?
分かってる？
（スマイル）知らないよ
Whatever.
違(ちげ)えよ
C'mon, man! Peco only listens to you, and thanks to Peco, we're—
ペコ お前の言うことしか
聞かねえし—
ペコのことで俺ら…
（大田）コラ １年！
ダベってんじゃねえぞ！
Hey, first-years! Quit flapping your gums!
The third-years are here!
３年 来てんだろう　コラァ！
Yes, sir!
（部員たち）うっす！
Yes, sir.
うーっす…
Tsukimoto Makoto (Smile)
Right-Handed Shakehand
Racket: Double Reverse
Style: Chopper
Come on! Let me hear you, first-years!
（大田）
オラァ！ 声出せ １年！
Captain Yamada.
（小泉(こいずみ)）キャプテン山田(やまだ)
What is it?
（山田）何すか？
Has that chopper with the glasses always been on our team?
メガネのカットマン
あんな子 うちにいたっけ？
What are you talking about?
何 言ってんすか
今年 入った期待の２強の
１人じゃないですか
He's one of the two up-and-comers who joined this year.
片割れバックレちゃってるんで
小泉先生も何か言ってくださいよ
The other's skipping practice.
Please, Mr. Koizumi, give him a talking-to.
The penhold kid with the bowl cut?
（小泉）それペンのおかっぱの子？
（山田）はい
Yes.
練習イヤなら やめてもらえば？
If he doesn't wanna practice, get him to quit.
We can't do that.
そうはいきませんよ
あれでも うちのエースですから
He's our star player.
ミスターメガネは？
What about Mr. Glasses over there?
確かに月本(つきもと)も
ずぬけてはいますが—
Tsukimoto's good, for sure.
星野(ほしの)の相手ではないです
He's no match for Hoshino, though.
ウッソ～
You're kidding...
ペコなら 多分
小田急駅前の卓球場ですよ
Peco's probably at the table tennis hall near Odakyuu Station.
That's not what I'm asking.
そんなこと
聞いてんじゃねえんだよ
地図 描きますから
自分で行ってください
I'll draw you a map. You go.
（高村(たかむら)）何を？
What was that?!
別に僕は
ペコの保護者じゃないですから
I'm not Peco's guardian.
If you keep talkin' like that,
I'm seriously gonna haze you!
（大田）
お前 そんなこと言ってっと
マジ いじめっぞ コラァ！
Is Mr. Oota angry?
ミスター大田 荒れてる？
（山田）はい
星野と月本が入ったおかげで—
Yes. Since Hoshino and Tsukimoto came along, he's not a starter anymore.
レギュラー 外れましたからねえ
They know they're better than us.
２人は 自分たちの技術が
我々より長(た)けているのを—
知っていますから—
生意気です
It makes them cocky.
You're new here, aren't you?
（ペコ）新入りだろう？ あんた
（ドテチン）
でも10年は やってるよ
Yeah, but I've been playing for ten years.
中坊の あんたくらい
負かす自信もある
I'm sure I can beat a kid like you.
（ペコ）そういうこと言ってない
That's not what I meant.
俺 握らない相手とは打たないの
I don't play people who don't bet.
（ドテチン）
握るって何？ お金？
Bet what? Money?
オババ ４番台 借りるよ
Old lady, I'm borrowing Table Four!
I don't rent tables to gamblers.
（オババ）
金賭けるやつには貸さん
Hear that?
（ドテチン）聞いた？
（ペコ）ワンゲーム 千円ね
A thousand yen per game.
And FYI, I go by "Peco" around here.
ほれから俺
ここじゃ“ペコ”で通ってんだ
You can call me that too.
あんたも そろえてくれていい
ほんかし この勝負で
俺が勝ったら—
But if I win, you add a "mister."
ちゃんと〝さん〞くれろ
That's Mister Peco to you!
〝ペコさん〞　そう呼べ
Hoshino Yutaka (Peco)
Right-Handed Penhold
Racket: Soft Front
Style: Offensive, Close to Table
Hoshino Yutaka (Peco)
Right-Handed Penhold
Racket: Soft Front
Style: Offensive, Close to Table
A new age has dawned, and still I can't make a decision
My path is too straight for my taste, but I'll walk it
I can't choose just yet
I have to think about it
I have no idea what I want to do
I'm going crazy!
Comparing yourself to others just makes you depressed
You're alone in this world
You're always alone here
Still you're gonna do it, right?
Maybe there's nothing that only I can do
But there's no way that I
But there's no way that I won't try to leave my mark
I just want to have my fun, whatever the times
（ドテチン）ううっ えい！
Yeah!
よっしゃーい！ ヒッヒー！
Damn it.
次
（ドテチン）えい！ えい…
（ドテチン）おおお…
（ペコ）よっしゃーい！
Yeah!
ううう…
ふざけたマネしやがって
Quit messing around!
What does it matter, as long as I win?
勝ちゃあいいんだが　勝ちゃあ
（ペコ）ひゃーっは！
（オババ）
よお スマイル 珍しいね
Hey, Smile.
You don't drop by often.
誰？
Who's that?
A newcomer.
新入りだよ
Said he made it pretty far in middle school.
中学のころ いいところまで
行ったとか何とか言ってるけど—
But he plays like a rich college kid.
しょせん 大学のボンボン卓球だね
（ドテチン）ええい！
えい！
（ペコ）えい！
（ドテチン）ナメやがって！
You're making a fool out of me!
Having fun at your club?
楽しいかい？ 部活は
Not really.
別に
The game is the same wherever I play it.
どこで打っても変わらないよ
That's not true, Smile.
それは違うよ スマイル
I didn't want you to go to that school. You deserve better.
私は お前に—
あの程度の学校
入ってほしくなかったね
Don't think too highly of me, old lady.
買いかぶらないでよ オババ
（ドテチン）えい！
（ペコ）おい！
（ドテチン）あああ…
Yeah!
っしゃー！
I don't like it when people do that.
迷惑なんだ そういうの
Did you think over my offer to coach kids?
子供のコーチの件は
考えてくれたかい？
無理だよ
子供って何するか分からないし—
I can't teach kids.
I never know what they're going to do, and I don't like them.
嫌いだし
（ドテチン）えい
もらった！
Gotcha!
Yeah!
っしゃー！
（ドテチン）ゼロバウンド…
No bounce...
（ペコ）俺に挑戦するの
３世紀 早まったね
It's about three centuries too soon for you to challenge me.
What were my ten years of effort for?!
俺の10年の努力は いったい…
Hard work is for chumps with no talent.
努力なんて
才能のないやつがするもんさ
Once I'm out of high school, I'm going to Europe.
俺 高校ハネったら
ヨーロッパ行く構えよ
俺が卓球で てっぺん取ったら—
If I make it to the top, this place'll gain some prestige, right, old lady?
この道場にも箔(はく)付くね オババ
That's the same cliché all snotty-nosed kids use, Peco.
そういうのはね ペコ
ハナタレの抜かす常とう句だよ
あしたは部活おいでね ペコ
Come to the club tomorrow, Peco.
Leaving already?
（ペコ）
もう帰るん？ 打ってかねえの？
You're not gonna play?
どうでもいいことだけどさ—
I don't care either way,
but they asked me to tell you, so I did.
言うように頼まれたから 一応
（オババ）しんどいだろうね
ああいう生き方も
It must be exhausting to live like that.
I do like that side of him,
あいつの
いいとこでも あんだけど—
but even I don't want him to be like that forever.
俺としても いつまでも
あの調子じゃ困んだよね
もう中坊じゃねえし
We're not in middle school anymore.
Do you call him "Smile" because he never smiles?
（ドテチン）
笑わないから“スマイル”？
Is he good?
強いの？
He's been my friend for a long time,
（ペコ）俺の昔からの
長いダチだかん—
so that's Mister Smile to you.
“スマイルさん”で
そろえてちょんまげ
So why don't you smile, Tsukimoto?
なんで笑わねえの？ 月本は
やっぱり あれ？
Are you makin' fun of us or what?
バカにしてんの？ 俺らのこと
Let it go, Oota.
よせ 大田
It makes me tired.
疲れるんですよ 何か
Laughing. Getting angry.
笑ったり 怒ったり
（大田）
ひょー！ かっちょいい～！
Well, aren't you cool!
Don't be stuck-up.
（高村）気取んなよ てめえ
C'mon, give it a rest.
（山田）もう よせって
先輩命令だ
This is an order from your elder.
Laugh.
笑え
（ペコ）ヒヒ… へーへッ
やっぱ子宮から１年早く
顔出した人間は偉いんすねえ
Dropping out of the womb a year earlier sure makes you high-and-mighty, doesn't it?
バカ よせ
Moron! Don't!
That first-year's totally picking a fight.
完璧に売っとるで あの１年
ナメやがって
よっしゃ 買ったらあ！
You wanna fight? I'll fight!
Hey, what are you doing?
（山田）おい 何やってんだよ
Now, now.
落ち着け
Calm down and go back to practicing.
練習 戻れよ　ほら
I asked you a question, idiot.
（ペコ）質問してんだよ スカタン
What?!
星野も もうよせ
Hoshino, stop.
Ribbit, ribbit.
ケロケ～ロ～
妬(や)いてんだ あいつら
They're jealous because they
can't beat you at table tennis.
卓球じゃ おめえに勝てねえから
コンデンスミルク吸ってたら
糖尿なるよ
If you keep drinking condensed milk, you'll get diabetes.
Let's ditch this pathetic practice and go to Tsujidou Academy instead.
こんな とろい部活バックレて
辻堂(つじどう)学院 行こうぜ
You know, to see China.
チャイナ 見によ
チャイナって…
China?
Tsujidou Academy brings in a Shanghai Junior League player as an exchange student
You mean the ringer they brought in from China?
中国から来た助っ人留学生？
That has nothing to do with us.
関係ないじゃん 僕らには
Smile, you're such a typical type B.
スマイルって
ホント 典型的Ｂ型だよね
Really?
そう？
If he played first string in his province,
省の一軍にいたってのは もう—
他の国の
ナショナルチームレベルなわけよ
that means he's at the same level as
the national teams of other countries.
（小泉）ハロー エブリバディ！
Hello, everybody.
Is everyone here?
（小泉）集合したかね？
（部員たち）うーっす！
Yes, sir!
（ペコ）ほら 見れ
お前がチンタラしてっから—
Look. Koizumi's turned up now because you took so long.
小泉 来ちゃったじゃん
Lessons, lessons.
レッスン レッスン
Tsukimoto's under pressure.
月本が押されてるよ
Yeah.
Hoshino really is good.
やっぱ うまいわ 星野
Shut up, you first-years!
抜いてんじゃねえぞ １年 コラァ！
（部員）あっ
（部員たち）うっす！
Yes, sir!
Question for you, Captain Yamada.
キャプテン山田にクエスチョン
ミスター月本は今日 不調？
Is Mr. Tsukimoto under the weather today?
Who knows? I haven't heard anything.
さあ 聞いてませんよ
なぜです？
Why?
（小泉）
やけにプレーがイージーだよ
He's not on his game.
（山田）ああ 相手が星野では
しかたがないですよ
That'd be because he's up against Hoshino.
（小泉）ああ？
（山田）練習態度は ともかく—
Huh?
His attitude toward practice aside, Hoshino's really good.
実際 星野は強いですよ
His footwork, his backhand,
his blocks. Everything, basically.
フットワーク　バック　ブロック
すべてにおいて
Have they known each other long?
長いの？ ２人
Tamura Table Tennis
（山田）駅前に タムラって
卓球道場 あるじゃないですか
You know Tamura, the tennis table hall near the station?
（小泉）あるねえ
Yeah.
They both got their start there.
（山田）
２人とも あそこの出身らしいです
（小泉）ああ そう
Really?
（山田）
ホント 楽しみですよ
今年のインハイ
I'm really excited to see how far
they'll go at this year's Interhigh.
あの２人が
どこまで行くか
No man so good, but another may be as good as he.
No man so good but another
may be as good as he.
What does that mean?
（山田）何です？ それ
“上には上がいる”という意味
That there's always someone better than you.
Hey, you first-years!
（大田）１年 コラァ！
（部員）はい！
Yes?
（大田）ちょっと来い コラァ！
Come here!
I haven't seen Tsukimoto or Hoshino for a while.
さっきから 俺の視界に
月本と星野が入らねえんだが—
What's going on?
どういうこと？
They said they were going to spy on China. Right?
あいつら何か
チャイナ スパイするとか言って…
（部員）なあ？
（部員）うん
Yeah. They went over to Tsujidou Academy.
辻堂学院 行きました
Get outside.
表 出ろ お前ら
外周 走って
ゲロ吐いてもらうわ
You're running laps until you puke.
Which kind of gum do you figure makes the biggest bubbles?
いちばん膨らむ風船ガムって
何だろう？
Dunno.
知らない
Bubblicious is good,
（ペコ）
バブリシャスもいいけど—
but Marukawa's cost-performance is right up there too.
マルカワも
コストパフォーマンス的には—
外せんよね
おめえもガム いる？
Want some gum?
No.
いらない
I wonder if Oota's making the first-years do laps right now.
今頃１年
大田に外周やらされてるかな
Probably.
（スマイル）多分
お前と一緒だと ホント楽しいよ
I have so much fun with you.
Never a dull conversation.
会話も弾むしね
次の駅？
Next stop?
The one after.
（スマイル）次の次
Is it cold outside?
How would I know? Figure it out yourself.
Damn.
I should've studied abroad in Europe.
Maybe Sweden or Germany.
It's a little late to say that now. Hurry it up, Wenge.
Kong Wenge
Right-Handed
Chinese Penhold
Racket: Double
Reverse Soft
Style: Offensive Drive
Kong Wenge
Right-Handed
Chinese Penhold
Racket: Double
Reverse Soft
Style: Offensive Drive
（顧問）かつては—
Tsujidou Academy was once the king of the east, but we've been getting weaker every year.
“東に辻高(つじこう)あり”と
うたわれたものでしたが—
年々 弱小の一途をたどりましてね
We did our meager best to come up with a plan,
私ども ない知恵絞って
一計を案じました結果—
and decided our best bet was to invite a first-class
player like Kong Wenge, and seek his direct guidance.
コン・ウェンガ君のような
一流の選手を招き—
じかに
その ご指導を仰ぐことこそ—
最善であるという結論に
達したわけでして…
What is this?
A folk dance?
He says he's learning a lot from watching how Japan plays.
（コーチ）“日本のプレーは
大変 参考になります”と
（生徒）
先生 ランニング行ってきます
Coach, we're going running.
Sure.
Wenge! They're going running!
This practice regimen is stupid.
If I play here, I'll get rusty in half a year.
彼 何と？
What did he say?
He's jet-lagged.
時差の疲れがありますので—
Would it be all right if he started tomorrow?
明日から始めて
よろしいでしょうか？
おお！
いや それはごもっともです
Oh, yes, of course.
That didn't occur to me.
気がつきませんで
Wait up, Smile.
待てよ スマイル
No Trespassing
Tsujidou Academy
Are you gonna just walk straight in?
お主 まさか正面堂々と行く気？
Yeah.
（スマイル）行く気　なんで？
Why not?
Why not? Because...
（ペコ）なんでって
そりゃ お前…
Well, whatever.
まあ いいけどさ
Is that the gym?
（スマイル）あれかな 体育館
Don't get full of yourself, Wenge.
Remember they're paying for you to be here!
It's not a problem, as long as I win.
That's some confidence you've got.
You saw those guys, right?
I could beat them with just my forehand.
If I'd known this'd happen, I would've given up sooner...
（ペコ）中(ちゅう)ペン
A Chinese penhold grip.
Kong Wenge?
コン・ウェンガ
ほーう これが本場の
中国製 粘着ラバー
So this is real Chinese sticky rubber.
全員 チャイナのカンフーで
抹殺されたのかね
Maybe China killed the whole team with his kung fu!
They're probably out running.
ランニングだよ きっと
ヘッ 何ちゅう練習メニューだ
そりゃ
What kind of training regimen is that?
これ いい台 使ってるな
They've got some nice tables.
This racket's got nice rubber on it too.
このペンもさ ほれ
いいラバー 貼ってんよ
And those losers aren't even good!
大した実力もねえくせによ
カーボン 入ってんし
It's even got a carbon blade.
Looks like Wenge's not here.
ウェンガもいないみたいだから
帰ろうよ
Let's go.
Huh?
ヒイ～
（スマイル）冗談だろ？
You've gotta be kidding me.
チャイナ来るまでの暇つぶしだ
Gotta kill time until China gets here.
I wanna return one of your chops with this baby!
こいつで
お前のカット さばいてみたいんよ
You hear that?
Yeah, that's a good chopper.
But the hitter is controlling the game.
He has speed.
Compared to the chopper, the attacker's play is sloppy.
But the chopper has his hands full just returning the ball.
Is the hitter getting a high arc?
No. He's got speed, but he leaves himself wide open.
The chopper's losing on purpose.
Why?
Who knows? Maybe it's a Japanese thing.
Anyway, let's head inside.
The wind makes it too hard to hear.
The Wind Makes it
Too Hard to Hear
Katase High! Fight! Fight! Fight!
（部員）ファイッ
（部員たち）オーッ
You're slowing down!
（大田）
ペース落ちてんぞ コラァ！
Mr. Tsukimoto's not here, Captain Yamada.
（小泉）ミスター月本がいないね
キャプテン山田
Faster!
He said he was going to spy
on Tsujidou Academy and left.
（山田）
辻堂学院にスパイに行くとか言って
帰っちゃいました
What?
（小泉）ふん？
It's just an excuse to skip practice.
（山田）
どうせ サボるための口実ですよ
Hoshino probably instigated it.
星野が誘ったんでしょう
（大田）声出せ １年！
Let me hear you, first-years!
Katase High! Fight! Fight!
（部員）片高！
（部員）ファイッ
（部員たち）オーッ
Captain, let them come back inside already.
（小泉）キャプテン
もう中に入れてやれよ
We're not the track team.
陸上部じゃないんだから
But...
（山田）いや しかし…
（大田）そうっすよ
That's right.
It's because you spoil them that
Tsukimoto and Hoshino take advantage!
先生が甘いから
星野や月本が甘えるんすよ
Well, let them off the hook for today.
（小泉）まあ 今日のバックレは
大目に見てやりな
Coach...
（山田）先生
（小泉）
中国が ラーメンとギョーザだけの
国じゃないことを—
It's a good chance for them to learn China's got more than just noodles and dumplings.
知るには いい機会だ
First-years, gather 'round!
１年 集合！
That's enough!
Keep playing like that and it'll become a habit, Glasses!
チャイナだ
It's China.
Holding back is disrespectful to your opponent.
He's trying to say—
つまり 彼が言うには…
You don't need to translate, Coach.
Glasses understands what I'm saying.
Right?
N-Ni hao.
ニ… ニーハオ！
Switch with me.
Kong wants to play.
（コーチ）コンが打ちたいそうだ
（ペコ）うほ！
Try chopping my strokes.
Xie xie.
（ペコ）シェー シェー！
Not you.
Wenge! Play him.
Tch.
（ペコ）ひょえ！
His speed varies like crazy.
（ペコの声）緩急 ありすぎ
（ペコ）ほい！
った…
There's heavy spin on that. Fast spin at that.
（ペコの声）よく曲がるねえ
スピードあるし
Is this like a "Super Drive" with 4,000 years of Chinese empire behind it?
これが中国４千年の
スーパードライブってか
I hear ya loud and clear!
了解 了解！
It's time...
来たー！
中国—
Eat this 4,000-year Super Drive!
４千—
年！
（ペコ）たら？
Huh?
He's got a sinking drive too?
（ペコの声）
沈むドライブもあんのかい
じゃあ今度は—
Then I'll hit it lower this time.
もっと下めで！
What did I do to deserve this?
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
That's a lot of spin.
（ペコの声）すっげえ回転
こりゃ かぶせて
当ててくっきゃねえか
I'll have to put some top spin on it.
I get kicked off the top team,
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
and then they toss me in with
crap players who wouldn't make second string?
Is this Hell?
（中国語の
チャイナの声）
Born in the country of table tennis,
I practiced more than enough.
I got results.
I supported my family.
But one little slip-up,
and now I'm stuck with these guys...
Your backhand is weak!
So is your forehand!
And your legs!
And your reactions!
Nothing you've got is good enough!
You don't deserve to be at the same table as me!
What did I do to deserve being thrown to end of the world?
Now learn...
how powerless...
and unpolished you are!
（スマイル）イレブンラブ
マッチ トゥ コン選手
Eleven-love.
The match goes to Kong.
I got skunked...
スコンクで負けた
Skunked!
ス… スコンクで… うっ…
You have a bad habit of crying after you lose.
（スマイル）
負けると泣くの 悪いクセだよ
帰ろう ペコ
Let's go, Peco.
You went too far.
I was just making him face reality.
Stand up. Come on.
（スマイル）さあ 立って ほら
Okay.
Wait, Glasses.
You, with the glasses.
メガネの子！
Show me your chops next.
Kong's interested in you.
コンは君に関心があるんだ
Would you do me a favor and play him?
相手をしてやってくれないか
It'd only end in defeat.
どうせ負けますから
He says no, because it would just end in defeat.
Whose defeat?!
Glasses has no fighting spirit.
It's a pity that he had no one to instill it in him.
That said,
maybe it's more of a pity to believe in a talent you don't have.
Wenge.
Let's practice.
If there are guys like him here,
then maybe there's still some hope left for me.
Annihilated
何？ それ
What's that?
Monster Robot.
モンスターロボ
I mean the song.
いや その歌
Is it weird?
（スマイル）変？
A little.
少しな
Next stop?
次の駅？
いや
No.
次の次
The one after.
A red sun stares at me
The world goes blurry when I yawn
My wishes fluctuate like a metronome
Everything tells me this is the end
I do have some dreams, you know
Sometimes we breathe
and just seem to inhale the smoke of someone
somewhere out of sight
Then all our great energy just seems to melt away
I don't understand this wonderland
I won't get wet even if it rains
This is a wonderland
Once I've made it through this long tunnel
I'm sure that someone will kiss me